

ENTRY LEVEL FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

# LUKAS DAUGĖLA

# **GET IN CONTACT**

Mobile: +370 60832132 lukasdaugela197@gmail.com

Kaunas portfolio: https://lukas-daugela.github.io/Portfolio

# PERSONAL PROFILE

Most of the time I used to work in constructions. After college I started to work as a

Construction Engineer, but after a while I realized, that this kind of job is not for me. Later I tried my self as a Supply Manager, but this job was mostly for building my self confidence and money so that I could start learning to make websites and after almost one year I started learning web development full time. Finished Vilnius Coding School and now looking for a job while developing my skills by creating various projects.

### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- · HTML, CSS experience
- JavaScript experience
- · Bootstrap experience
- I am able to make pixel perfect projects from psd or figma files
- English knowledge speaking b1 writing – b1

# **OTHER SKILLS**

- · Detail oriented
- Always making websites responsive to all devices
- I have passion and drive to expand my coding skills

# **EDUCATION HISTORY**

#### **ONLINE COURSE**

Udemy.com | 2022-06 - 2022-07

- HTML
- CSS
- Responsive websites

#### VILNIUS CODING SCHOOL

WEB full stack course | 2022-05 - 2022-06

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- PHP
- Wordpress

JAVA beginner course | 2020-08 - 2020-10

- JAVA basics
- JAVA OOP
- MySQL basics
- Android
- GIT

#### KAUNAS TECHNICAL COLLEGE

Bachelor of Civil Engineering | 2016 - 2019

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **SUPPLY MANAGER**

UAB "Kaunakiemis" | 2021-05 - 2022-04

- I coordinated and accepted supply orders
- I was responsible for filling bill of lading
- · I organized navigation routes for drivers

# **CONSTRUCTION ENGINEER**

UAB "Inžinieriai" | 2020-02 - 2020-07'

- Coordinated work operations with clients and construction workers
- Developed, prepared and executed work plans for the construction activities
- · Design and update construction drawings
- Filled in the work log